{
    "id": "31808113ca6c4b4cbfc56df1f19ae9a3",
    "title": "So Do I, Neither Do I | Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3cd61a94cdc248bc966a0bdad6eebe53",
            "title": "So do I and Neither do I",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "'I'm tired.' ................................",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "So do I.",
                        "So am I",
                        "Neither do I",
                        "Neither am I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I was late.' '....................................'",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "So do I",
                        "So was I",
                        "So did I",
                        "Neither do I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I didn't like that film.' '...............................'",
                    "description": "After adding a negative idea, we can add another negative idea using the expression 'neither did I' or 'neither am I'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "So did I",
                        "Neither did I",
                        "So am I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I didn't finish it.' '.................................'",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Neither did I",
                        "So did I",
                        "Neither was I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I like coffee.' '................................'",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. \r\n",
                    "answers": [
                        "So am I",
                        "So do I",
                        "Neither am I",
                        "Neither do I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I can swim.' '.................................'",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "So I can",
                        "So do I",
                        "So can I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I'm staying for another two days.' '...................................'",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "So I am",
                        "So do I",
                        "So am I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "'She has a degree in physics.' '..........................'",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "So do I",
                        "So have I",
                        "So has I",
                        "So did I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I don't have his number.' '...............................'",
                    "description": "After adding a negative idea, we can add another negative idea using the expression 'neither did I' 'neither have I' or 'neither am I'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Neither have I",
                        "So have I",
                        "Neither I have"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I found the problem very hard.' '...............................'",
                    "description": "The structure 'so do I' or 'so am I' is used to add to the sentence before. It uses the same auxiliary verb as in the previous sentence. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "So am I",
                        "So do I",
                        "So did I",
                        "So have I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Maria can sing beautifully and ...............................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so her sister can",
                        "so can her sister",
                        "neither can her sister"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "'I had never seen so much food in my life.' '..............................'",
                    "description": "After adding a negative idea, we can add another negative idea using the expression 'neither did I' or 'neither am I'.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Neither have I",
                        "Neither had I",
                        "Neither did I"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}